typesquare.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | TypeSquare

    * TypeSquare
    * Privacy Policy

Morisawa, Inc (“Morisawa,” “we,” us,” “our”) is concerned about privacy issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect through the website located at http://typesquare.com (the “Site”) as well as through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”). By providing Personal Information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Personal Information We May Collect

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, including: 

• Name

• Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses)

• Telephone number

• Email address

• Information relating to your business

We may use a third-party payment service to process payments made through the Services. If you wish to make a payment through the Services, your Personal Information may be collected by such third party and not by us, and will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, this third party’s collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information. 

### How We May Collect Personal Information

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including: 

• Through the Services: We may collect Personal Information through the Services, e.g., when you sign up for an account or make an inquiry. 

• Offline: We may collect Personal Information from you offline, such as when you interact with us at trade shows or contact customer service. 

• From Other Sources: We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases; joint marketing partners; social media platforms; and other third parties. 

### How We May Use Personal Information

We may use Personal Information: 

• To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters. 

• To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. 

• To complete and fulfill your purchase, for example to communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service. To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you. 

• To personalize your experience on the Services by presenting products and offers tailored to you. 

• For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities. 

• As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

### How Personal Information May Be Disclosed

Your Personal Information may be disclosed: 

• To our affiliate, Morisawa USA Inc., for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Morisawa Inc. is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information. 

• To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, credit card processing, auditing and other similar services. 

• To third parties to permit them to send you marketing communications, consistent with your choices 

• To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

• As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

## OTHER INFORMATION

### Other Information We May Collect

“Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: 

• Browser and device information

• Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies

• Demographic information and other information provided by you

• Aggregated information

### How We May Collect Other Information

We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including: 

• Through your browser or device: Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type and version and the name and version of the Services you are using. We use this information to ensure that the Services function properly. 

• Using cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Services, pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Services, as well as for online tracking purposes. We can recognize your computer to assist your use of the Services. We also gather statistical information about the usage of the Services in order to continually improve the design and functionality, understand how the Services are used and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the Services. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.> However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer and you may need to log in every time you visit the applicable Services. 

• Analytics. We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Services and report on activities and trends.  This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources.  You can learn about Google’s practices by going to <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>, and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

• Using Adobe Flash technology (including Flash Local Shared Objects (“Flash LSOs”)) and other similar technologies: We may use Flash LSOs and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Services. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the [Website Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the [Global Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html) and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to as “information” on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including those used in connection with the Services. 

• Using pixel tags and other similar technologies: Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the actions of users of the Services (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Services and response rates. 

• IP Address: Your “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Services, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels of the Services, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Services. 

• From you: Information such as your preferred means of communication is collected when you voluntarily provide this information. 

• By aggregating information: Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Services, (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code). 

### How We May Use and Disclose Other Information

Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. 

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. If we combine any Other Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

## THIRD PARTY SERVICES

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates. 

## SECURITY

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the _“Contacting Us”_ section below. 

## CHOICES AND ACCESS

### Your choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information

We give you choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from: 

• Receiving electronic communications from us: If you no longer want to receive marketing‑related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these marketing‑related emails by visiting https://typesquare.com/question/. 

• Our sharing of your Personal Information with affiliates for their direct marketing purposes: If you would prefer that we not share your Personal Information on a going-forward basis with our affiliates for their direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of this sharing by visiting https://typesquare.com/question/. 

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. If you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages. 

### How you can access, change or suppress your Personal Information

If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, or delete Personal Information that has been previously provided to us by you, you may submit your request on the Typesquare website (https://typesquare.com/question/). 

In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal Information. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 

We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion. There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. 

## RETENTION PERIOD

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

## USE OF SERVICES BY MINORS

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Services. 

## CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than those of your country. 

## SENSITIVE INFORMATION

We ask that you not send us, or disclose, any sensitive Personal Information ( _e.g._ , social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Services or otherwise to us. 

## UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy. The _“LAST UPDATED”_ legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at https://typesquare.com/question/, or please write to the following address: 

795 Folsom St. 1F San Francisco CA 94107 USA

Please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your messages to us.
